Every story has a beginning. A middle. And an end.
Brotherhood is a crime, drama film directed by Noel Clarke.
First there was Kidulthood then Adulthood now comes Noel Clarkes last installment brotherhood With Sam facing up to the new world he realizes it also
comes with new problems and new challenges that he must face that he knows will require old friends to help him survive new dangers.
Sam Peel, played by Noel Clarke.
Henry, played by Arnold Oceng.
Kayla, played by Shanika Warren-Markland.
Agnes Peel, played by Adjoa Andoh.
Uncle Curtis, played by Cornell John.
Alisa, played by Red Madrell.
Brotherhood (stylised as BrOTHERHOOD) is a 2016 British crime drama
film written, produced and directed by Noel Clarke.
It is the sequel to 2006's Kidulthood and 2008's Adulthood, and
the third and final instalment of The Hood Trilogy.
It stars Clarke, Jason Maza (who also co-produced the film), Arnold Oceng, Stormzy,
Cornell John, David Ajala, Shanika Warren-Markland and Adjoa Andoh.
Brotherhood follows Sam (Clarke), now a family man of two
children, being driven back to his criminal lifestyle.
Clarke initially did not want to make a third film, but eventually returned in 2015
to write, direct and star in the third film of his Hood Trilogy.
Filming began in London in November.
Brotherhood was screened in the Special Presentations section at the 2016 Toronto
International Film Festival and was released on 29 August 2016.
The film received mixed-to-positive reviews and becoming
the highest-grossing film in the trilogy.
The film explores themes of london, england, ghetto, hood, gang.
The tone is emotional.